Good afternoon Oh We need a flag of Russia from
Добрый день Ой Нам нужен флаг России из
Ukraine the city of Khmelnitsky the high
Украины город Хмельницкий высокого
city of Russia the
города России
city of
город
Ukraine the city of Khmelnitsky which
Украины город Хмельницкий вы с какого
city of Russia
города России
are you from again and we are from Russia Saratov Everything is
еще раз а мы Мы из России Саратов Все
super how are you doing Saratov
супер как там у вас дела Саратове
I heard that a
Я слышал что там из самарии Саратова
lot of people died in Makeyevka from Samaria Saratov  before the soldiers from the
много погибло в Макеевке до солдат от
blow
удара
, one of your friends is fighting in Ukraine, your
у вас кто-то из знакомых воюет в Украине
best friend,
лучший друг
in your opinion, why did you
по вашему мнению из-за чего Ради чего
fight for the Motherland in a foreign country? Yes, but
за Родину в чужой стране воевал Да но
because of what all this happened because
из-за чего все это произошло из-за того
Zelensky said on February 23  wrong speech, that
Зеленский произнес неправильную речь то
is, it turns out your friend died due to
есть получается ваш друг погиб из-за
the fact that for the sake of the fact that Zelensky had to
того что ради того что Зеленского надо
be punished for wrong speech,
было наказать за неправильную речь так
well, why did he die
ну ради чего погиб
?  They decide their own
вот политики политики себе свои решают А
But your boyfriend That's the essence of
вот ваш парень Знакомый вот в чем суть
his death It was for what, for example,
его смерти было Вот ради чего например
when the Germans came to our Earth, our
когда немцы пришли на нашу Землю наши
grandfathers defended our Earth from the Germans for
деды защищали нашу Землю от немцев ради
which your boyfriend sent  and to a foreign
чего вашего парня отправили в чужую
country, that's why How can we
страну вот ради чего Как мы можем
answer this question If we, too, are
ответить на этот вопрос Если мы тоже как
like
бы
this What do you think What mother thinks
вот Как вы считаете Какие мама считает
that he is there
что он там
Well, to say he defended his homeland will not work
Ну сказать родину защищал не получится
because he was born defended in a foreign
потому что он родился защищал в чужой
homeland somehow True,
Родине как-то Правда
he fell for  his homeland in a foreign country
он упал за свою Родину в чужой стране
He did not choose where he would be sent Well, yes,
Он же не выбирал куда его отправит Ну да
well, that's why he was sent to a foreign
ну вот зачем его отправили в чужую
homeland
родину
in order, for example, to save people from
для того чтобы например спасти людей с
captivity what captivity there was no war there was no
плен каких плена не было войны не было
captivity of
плена
familiar friends
знакомых друзей
Well, it turns out What is the meaning of death
Ну получается В чем смысл смертью
For example, if he is there  I was supposed to
Например если он там должен был
release Zelensky in short there and kill Zelensky there,
освободить короче там Зеленского и там
what was the purpose of the person
убить зеленскому цель какая была человек
here you are sitting in chat roulette in order
вот вы сидите в чат рулетке для того
to talk politics talk about
чтобы поговорить политике говорить о
politics and tell people that they
политике и сказать людям о том что у них
died there Relatives friends brothers
погибли там Родственники друзья братья
sisters
сестры
husbands sons this is for him Speak for what
мужья сыновья это ему Говорите Для чего
for  to do something
для того чтобы им делать как-то
unpleasant for them No, I want to understand, look, I
неприятно Нет я хочу понять вот смотри я
can’t understand for 10 months people from
не могу понять вот 10 месяцев люди из
Russia come, they come to Ukraine
России приезжайте приезжают в Украину
to fight I couldn’t  to understand why they
воевать Я не могу понять ради чего они
are doing this, no one can give an answer
это делают никто не может дать ответ
And how do you and we also do not understand why they
И как вы и мы тоже не понимаем зачем это
are doing this, do you think they know why they are
делают вы думаете они знают зачем их
sent to another country to
отправляют на другую страну чтобы они
fight I don’t think that they also want to
воевали Я не думаю что они тоже хотят
kill people and die on their own, it
убивать людей и умирать самим то
turns out  your government sends them But
получается ваша власть их отправляет Но
it doesn’t explain to you why it sends them
вам не объясняет зачем она их отправляет
to Ukraine I don’t listen to the news I’m
в Украину я не слушаю новости Мне это
not interested at all Tomorrow they’ll
вообще не интересно Еще завтра возьмут
take your dad, for example,
вашего папу отправит например
it’s not good for me, for example, there’s a friend
мне нет хорошо например там друга еще
there, send someone else there
кого-то там отправить
I don’t understand, it turns out Putin sends
Я не понимаю получается Путин отправляет
people But  doesn’t even explain to them Why he
людей Но даже не объясняет им Зачем он
sends people to Ukraine
отправляет людей в Украину погибает
and who dies And who is it
А кто
But your president our president doesn’t
Но ваш президент наш президент вас не
send you he can’t send you to
отправляет он не может Вас отправить в
Ukraine because you can’t get
Украину так потому что вы не можете
to Russia in any way so look here
никак до России добраться так смотри вот
we are sitting in Ukraine
мы сидим себе в Украине
This is the
Это главный вопрос
girl’s main question  why yours are dying here
девушки за что дохнут ваши вот эти
they are sitting
они сидят
we don’t know we don’t know
мы не знаем мы не зна